Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Individuals PE.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- K, 1889-2008; 3.25 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Kuczynski, Jürgen, 1938 (Box 15)
  - Kugler, Israel, 1917-2007, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Kuhn, Maggie, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Kun, Bela, undated (Box 15)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 15)
  - Kutcher, James, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Kuusinen, Otto Vilhelm, undated (Box 15)
  - Kuzminov, I., 1948 (Box 15)
- L, 1893-2008; 3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - La Follette, Philip Fox, 1897-1965 (Box 15)
  - La Follette, Robert M., 1924, undated (Box 15)
  - La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947 (Box 15)
  - Labadie, Jo, 1850-1933, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Labadie, Laurance, 1934 (Box 15)
  - Lacaze-Duthiers, Gérard de, b. 1876, 1932 (Box 15)
  - Lafargue, Paul, 1842-1911, 1936 (Box 15)
  - Laidler, Harry Wellington, 1884-1970, 1925 (Box 15)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1902-, 1949- (Box 15)
  - Lamont, Thomas W. (Thomas William), 1870-1948, 1942 (Box 15)
  - Landauer, Gustave, undated (Box 16)
  - Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987, 1936 (Box 16)
  - Landry, Sy, 2007 (Box 16)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1894-1956, 1941 (Box 16)
  - Lang, Lucy Robins, 1962 (Box 16)
  - Lange, Dorothea, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Lannon, Al, 1947 (Box 16)
  - Lara, Alejandro Molina, 1983 (Box 16)
  - LaRouche, Lyndon H., 1985 (Box 16)
  - LaRouche, Lyndon H.: LaRouche Campaign, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Laski, Harold Joseph, 1893-1950 (Box 16)
  - Lasky, Melvin J., 1951, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Lassalle, Ferdinand, 1825-1864, 1893 (Box 16)
  - Latimer, Lewis H., 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1900-1989, 1946 (Box 16)
  - Laurence, William L., 1950 (Box 16)
  - Laurens, Henry, 1724-1792, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Lawe, John E., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Lawson, James, 1883-, 1919 (Box 16)
  - Le Sueur, Meridel, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Lee, Algernon, 1943 (Box 16)
  - Leech, E. T., undated (Box 16)
  - Leffingwell, William Henry, 1876-1934, 1909 (Box 16)
  - Leggett, Sonya, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Lehane, Cornelius, 1919 (Box 16)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963, 1953 (Box 16)
  - Lenin, Nicolai, 1918 (Box 16)
  - Lenin, Vladimir Ilyich, 1870-1924 I, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lenin, Vladimir Ilyich, 1870-1924 II, 1917 (Box 16)
  - Lens, Sidney, 1961 (Box 16)
  - Lermond, Norman W., 1944 (Box 16)
  - Lerner, Max, 1902-, 1938 (Box 16)
  - Lerner, Michael, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Leroux, Pierre, 1897 (Box 16)
  - Leval, Gastón, undated (Box 16)
  - Levene, Alexander, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Levi, Paul, 1921 (Box 16)
  - Levin, Meyer, 1905-1981, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Levin, Samuel M., 1932 (Box 16)
  - Leviné, Eugen, 1919 (Box 16)
  - Levin-Shatzkes, Icchok, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Levinson, Edward, 1938 (Box 16)
  - Levitas, Samuel M., 1950 (Box 16)
  - Levitt, Alfred, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Lewis, Fulton, 1903-1966 (Box 16)
  - Lewis, John Llewellyn, 1880-1969, 1937 (Box 16)
  - Leyda, Jay, 1910-1988, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Lichnowsky, Karl Max, Fürst von, 1860-1928, 1918 (Box 16)
  - Lichtheim, George, 1912-, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Lieberman, Chaim, undated (Box 16)
  - Liebknecht, Karl Paul August Friedrich, 1871-1919, undated (Box 16)
  - Liebknecht, Wilhelm, undated (Box 16)
  - Liefmann, Robert, 1874-1941, 1922 (Box 16)
  - Lightfoot, Claude M., 1910-1991, 1954 (Box 16)
  - Lilienthal, David Eli, 1899-1981, 1939 (Box 16)
  - Lilienthal, Meta Stern, 1876-1948, undated (Box 16)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865, 1900 (Box 17)
  - Lincoln, Murray D., 1966 (Box 17)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles August), 1859-1924, 1916 (Box 17)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles Augustus), 1902-1974, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Linder, Marc, 2001 (Box 17)
  - Lindsay, John V., undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1915 (Box 17)
  - Lipset, Seymour Martin, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Lissner, Will, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Little, Frank, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Little, Joan, 1973 (Box 17)
  - Liuzzo, Viola, 1925-1965, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Lloyd, Henry Demarest, 1847-1903, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Lobman, Ethel, 1999 (Box 17)
  - London, Jack, 1876-1916 I, 1905 (Box 17)
  - London, Jack, 1876-1916 II, 1905 (Box 17)
  - London, Meyer, 1871-1926, 1939, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Long, Hamilton A., undated (Box 17)
  - Long, Huey Pierce, 1893-1935, undated (Box 17)
  - Loo, P. E., 1947 (Box 17)
  - Lord, Clifford Lee, 1912-, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Lore, Ludwig, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Lorwin, Lewis Levitzki, 1883-1970, 1913 (Box 17)
  - Lott, Edison S., 1916 (Box 17)
  - Lovell, Frank, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Lovestone, Jay, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Low, Bela, 1943 (Box 17)
  - Lowenfels, Walter, 1897-1976, undated (Box 17)
  - Lowenthal, Richard, 1961 (Box 17)
  - Lucas, Jim G., undated (Box 17)
  - Lucia, Carmen, 1902-, 1951 (Box 17)
  - Lucy, William, circa 1972 (Box 17)
  - Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1879-1962, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Lukács, György, 1885-1971, 1957 (Box 17)
  - Lukes, Steven, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Lumer, Hyman, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Lumpkin, Beatrice, 2008 (Box 17)
  - Lundeen, Ernest, 1878-1940, 1933 (Box 17)
  - Luppol, I., 1930 (Box 17)
  - Luxemburg, Rosa, 1871-1919, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Lynd, Staughton, 1964 (Box 17)
  - Lyons, A. Neil (Albert Neil), 1880-1940, undated (Box 17)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1898-, undated (Box 17)
  - Lyons, John, 1909 (Box 17)
  - Lysenko, Trofim Denisovich, 1898-1976, 1949 (Box 17)
  - Lyttle, Bradford, 1966 (Box 17)
- M, 1884-2002; 4 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes
  - Maas, Elmer, undated (Box 17)
  - Maas, Melvin Joseph, 1898-1964, 1944 (Box 17)
  - Mabry, Samuel, 1960 (Box 17)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1880-1964, 1963, undated (Box 17, Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Macdonagh, Thomas, circa 1918 (Box 17)
  - Macdonald, Dwight, 1963 (Box 17)
  - MacDonald, James Ramsay, 1866-1937, undated (Box 17)
  - MacMahon, Douglas L., 1942 (Box 17)
  - Machel, Samora, undated (Box 17)
  - Maeckel, Herman J., 1917 (Box 17)
  - Maguire, Mathew, 1894 (Box 17)
  - MacQueen, William, 1905 (Box 17)
  - Maguire, Michael, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Mailly, Bertha Howell, 1959 (Box 18)
  - Mailly, William, 1871-1912, 1910 (Box 18)
  - Mainardi, Pat, undated (Box 18)
  - Maisel, Albert Q., 1945 (Box 18)
  - Makarenko, Anton Semenovich, 1888-1939 (Box 18)
  - Makatini, Mfanafuthi Johnstone, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Malatesta, Errico, 1853-1932 (Box 18)
  - Malcolm X, 1925-1965, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Malinowski, Wladyslaw Roman, 1909-, 1944 (Box 18)
  - Malmgreen, Gail, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Malone, Maud, 1951 (Box 18)
  - Malonzo, Cipriano C., 1959 (Box 18)
  - Malraux, André, 1901-1976, 1937 (Box 18)
  - Maltz, Albert, 1908-1985 (Box 18)
  - Mandel, Ernst, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Mandel, William, undated (Box 18)
  - Mandela, Nelson, 1918-, 1964-1985 (Box 18, Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Manion, Clarence E., 1963 (Box 18)
  - Mann, Tom, 1856-1941, 1936 (Box 18)
  - Manning, William, 1923 (Box 18)
  - Manson, Julius J., 1956 (Box 18)
  - Manz, Karl, 1918 (Box 18)
  - Mao, Zedong, 1893-1976, 1954 (Box 18)
  - Marcantonio, Vito, 1902-1954 I, 1935, undated (Box 18, Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Marcantonio, Vito, 1902-1954 II, 1935 (Box 18)
  - Marcy, Mary E., 1922 (Box 18)
  - Marcy, Sam, 1911-, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Margulies, Max, undated (Box 18)
  - Marighella, Carlos, undated (Box 18)
  - Marini, Giovanni, undated (Box 18)
  - Marishka, Valeena, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Maritain, Jacques, 1882-1973, 1943 (Box 18)
  - Markham, Edwin, 1852-1940, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Markow, I., undated (Box 18)
  - Marroquin, Hector (Defense Committee), 1978 (Box 18, Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Marshall, "Critter" Craig, undated (Box 18)
  - Marshall, Ray, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Marshall, Verne, 1889-1965, 1941 (Box 18)
  - Martí, José, 1853-1895, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Martin, David, 1959 (Box 18)
  - Martin, Don, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Martin, Harold H., 1962 (Box 18)
  - Martin, Josephine D., 2000 (Box 18)
  - Martin, Kingsley, 1897-1969, undated (Box 18)
  - Martinson, Robert, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Marty, Andre, 1940 (Box 18)
  - Marx, Karl, 1818-1883 I, 1921 (Box 18)
  - Marx, Karl, 1818-1883 II, 1921 (Box 18)
  - Marx, Karl, 1818-1883 III, 1921 (Box 18)
  - Marx, Karl, 1818-1883 IV, 1921 (Box 18)
  - Marx, Karl, 1818-1883 V, 1921 (Box 18)
  - Marzani, Carl, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Massari, Vincent, 1943 (Box 18)
  - Mast, Robert H., 1928-, circa 1994 (Box 18)
  - Mather, Alan W., 1935 (Box 18)
  - Mathews, Virginia H., 1965 (Box 18)
  - Matles, James J., 1942 (Box 18)
  - Matusow, Harvey, 1926-, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Maurer, James H. (James Hudson), b. 1864, 1912 (Box 18)
  - Maurer, Mary Jane, 1943 (Box 18)
  - Max, Alan, undated (Box 18)
  - Max, Steve, undated (Box 18)
  - Mayer, Milton, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Mayer, Milton Sanford, 1908-, 1949 (Box 18)
  - Mboya, Tom, 1956 (Box 18)
  - McBride, Sylvester J., circa 1931 (Box 18)
  - McCabe, Louis F., 1964 (Box 18)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J., 1916-2005, 1968 (Box 18)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1908-1957 I, 1952 (Box 19)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1908-1957 II, 1952 (Box 19)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1908-1957 III, 1954 (Box 19)
  - McClatchy, V. S. (Valentine Stuart), 1857-1938, 1922 (Box 19)
  - McCloy, John J. (John Jay), 1895-1989, 1961 (Box 19)
  - McClure, S. S. (Samuel Sidney), 1857-1949, undated (Box 19)
  - McCulloch, Frank W., 1905-1996, 1961 (Box 19)
  - McDonald, Dave, 1958 (Box 19)
  - McDonald, Grace, undated (Box 19)
  - McDonald, Lee Cameron, undated (Box 19)
  - McDowell, Mary E., undated (Box 19)
  - McDowell, Mary S., 1955 (Box 19)
  - McGee, Willie, 1950 (Box 19)
  - McGill, Ralph, 1898-1969, 1961 (Box 19)
  - McGovern, George, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Box 35, Folder 14)
  - McGrady, Thomas, 1863-1907, 1901 (Box 19)
  - McGuire, P. J. (Peter James), 1852-1906, 1885-1968 (Box 19)
  - McGurn, Barrett, 1963 (Box 19)
  - McKie, Bill, 1949 (Box 19)
  - McKinney, Ernest Rice, 1984 (Box 19)
  - McKinney, Robert, 1960 (Box 19)
  - McLaughlin, Brian M., 2002 (Box 19)
  - McLevy, Jasper, 1878-1962, 1935 (Box 19)
  - McMichael, Jack, 1941 (Box 19)
  - McNamara, James B. (James Barnabas), 1882-1941 (Box 19)
  - McNamara, John J., undated (Box 19)
  - McNamara, Patrick Vincent, 1894-1966, 1958 (Box 19)
  - McNeill, Marion Lucius, undated (Box 19)
  - McNutt, Paul V. (Paul Vories), 1891-1955, undated (Box 19)
  - McReynolds, David, 1958, undated (Box 19, Box 35, Folder 15)
  - McSorley, William J., 1951 (Box 19)
  - McWilliams, Carey, 1905-1980, 1945 (Box 19)
  - McWilliams, Joseph E., undated (Box 19)
  - Mead, Margaret, undated (Box 19)
  - Meany, George, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Medina, Harold R. (Harold Raymond), 1888-, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Medonis, Robert X., Jr., 1994 (Box 19)
  - Meiggs, Henry, undated (Box 19)
  - Meir, Golda, 1898-1978, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Melish, William Howard, 1910-, 1943 (Box 19)
  - Melman, Seymour, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Melville, Sam, undated (Box 19)
  - Mendelson, Wilfred, 1915-1938, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Mendoza, José Luis, 1948 (Box 19)
  - Merchant, Francis, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Meredith, James H., 1962 (Box 19)
  - Merriam, Eve, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Merton, Thomas, 1915-1968, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Mesta, Perle, ca. 1890-1975, undated (Box 19)
  - Meyer, Frank S., undated (Box 19)
  - Meyer, Gerald, 1940-, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Meyer, Peter I, 1943 (Box 19)
  - Meyer, Peter II, 1953 (Box 19)
  - Meyers, George, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Michel, Louise, 1830-1905, undated (Box 19)
  - Mihailović, Draža, 1893-1946 (Box 19)
  - Mihajlov, Mihajlo, 1934-, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Mije, Antonio, 1940 (Box 19)
  - Milgram, Sarah, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Miller, Arthur, 1923-, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Miller, Clyde R., 1962 (Box 19)
  - Miller, David J., 1966 (Box 19)
  - Miller, Harold V., 1954 (Box 19)
  - Miller, Moses, 1949 (Box 19)
  - Miller, Spencer, 1891-, 1924 (Box 19)
  - Mills, C. Wright (Charles Wright), 1916-1962, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Mills, Walter Thomas, 1856-1942, undated (Box 19)
  - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1951 (Box 19)
  - Minami, Shuhei, undated (Box 19)
  - Mindszenty, Jozsef, 1892-1975, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Minor, Robert, 1884-1952, 1919 (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, Charlene, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, David H., 1965 (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, H. L. (Harry Leland), 1906-1989, 1943 (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, John, 1870-1919, undated (Box 19)
  - Mitford, Jessica, 1917-1996 (Box 19)
  - Molina, Francisco (Committee to Defend), 1961 (Box 19)
  - Mollet, Guy, 1905-1975, 1957 (Box 20)
  - Molnar, Erik, undated (Box 20)
  - Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942 I, 1918 (Box 20)
  - Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942 II, 1918 (Box 20)
  - Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942 III, 1918 (Box 20)
  - Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942: Molders Defense Committee, 1931-1939 (Box 20)
  - Moore, Audley, 1898-, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Moravec, František, 1895 or 6-1966 (Box 20)
  - Moreau, Alberto, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Moreira, Juan, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Morgan, Lewis Henry, 1818-1881, 1916 (Box 20)
  - Morgan, Thomas J., 1898 (Box 20)
  - Morgan, W. S., undated (Box 20)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, undated (Box 20)
  - Morris, Edwin, undated (Box 20)
  - Morris, George, 1903-, 1945 (Box 20)
  - Morris, William, 1834-1896 I, 1884 (Box 20)
  - Morris, William, 1834-1896 II, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Morrison, Herbert, 1888-1965, undated (Box 20)
  - Morrison, Herbert M., 1936 (Box 20)
  - Morrison, Norman R., 1933-1965 (Box 20)
  - Morse, Wayne L. (Wayne Lyman), 1900-1974, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Mortimer, Wyndham, undated (Box 20)
  - Morton, James F. (James Ferdinand), 1870-1941, undated (Box 20)
  - Moses, Robert Parris, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Moskow, Michael H., undated (Box 20)
  - Mosley, Oswald, 1896-1980, 1934 (Box 20)
  - Most, Johann Joseph, 1846-1906, undated (Box 20)
  - Motley, Constance Baker, 1921-, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Mowery, Edward J., 1959 (Box 20)
  - Mowrer, Edgar Ansel, 1892-1977, 1943 (Box 20)
  - Moyer, Charles H., 1907 (Box 20)
  - Moyer, William, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Moynahan, Daniel Patrick, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Mühsam, Erich, undated (Box 20)
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990, 1959 (Box 20)
  - Mundt, Karl E., 1950 (Box 20)
  - Muñoz, V., undated (Box 20)
  - Munsell, A. E. O. (Alexander Ector Orr), 1951, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949, undated (Box 20)
  - Murray, Philip, 1886-1952, 1940 (Box 20)
  - Murray, James E., 1938 (Box 20)
  - Mussolini, Benito, 1883-1945, 1928 (Box 20)
  - Muste, Abraham John, 1885-1967 I, 1951 (Box 20)
  - Muste, Abraham John, 1885-1967 II (Box 20)
  - Muzzey, David Saville, 1870-1965, undated (Box 20)
  - Myers, Gustavus, 1872-1942, circa 1908 (Box 20)
  - Myers, James, b. 1882, 1937 (Box 20)
  - Mygatt, Tracy, undated (Box 20)
  - Mylius, Edward F., 1913 (Box 20)
- N, 1901-2004; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Nader, Ralph, 2004
  - Naft, Stephen, 1878-1956, 1943 (Box 20)
  - Nagel, Ernest, 1901-, undated (Box 20)
  - Nagler, Isidore, 1895-, 1959 (Box 20)
  - Nagy, Imre, 1896-1958 (Box 20)
  - Nash, Al, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Nasmyth, George, undated (Box 20)
  - Natorps, Paul, undated (Box 20)
  - Naud, Albert, undated (Box 20)
  - Neal, Fred Warner, 1960 (Box 20)
  - Neal, William S., 1926 (Box 20)
  - Nearing, Scott, 1883-1983, 1915 (Box 21)
  - Nedoshivin, G., 1951 (Box 21)
  - Nehru, Jawaharlal, 1889-1964, 1941, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Neider, Charles, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Neilson, Francis, 1867-, 1961 (Box 21)
  - Nelles, Walter, 1883-1937, 1928 (Box 21)
  - Neruda, Pablo, 1904-1973, 1945 (Box 21)
  - Nettlau, Max, 1865-1944, 1901 (Box 21)
  - Neuberger, Richard L. (Richard Lewis), 1912-1960, undated (Box 21)
  - Neuberger, Samuel, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Neumann, Franz, undated (Box 21)
  - Newman, James R., 1962 (Box 21)
  - Newman, Joseph, 1950 (Box 21)
  - Newman, Pauline, 1921 (Box 21)
  - Newport, Eugene "Gus", 1985 (Box 21)
  - Newton, Huey P., 1968 (Box 21, Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Nicolaevsky, Boris I., 1887-1966, 1961 (Box 21)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1892-1971, 1931 (Box 21)
  - Ninfo, Salvatore, 1883-1960 (Box 21)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994, undated (Box 21)
  - Nixon, Russell, undated (Box 21)
  - Nkrumah, Kwame, 1909-1972, undated (Box 21)
  - Nock, Albert Jay, 1872 or 3-1945, undated (Box 21)
  - Nomad, Max, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Norden, Albert, undated (Box 21)
  - Norman, William, undated (Box 21)
  - Norris, George W. (George William), 1861-1944, 1942 (Box 21)
  - Northrup, Herbert Roof, 1918-2007, 1942 (Box 21)
  - Novack, George Edward, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Novik, Morris S., 1903-, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Novik, P., 1891-, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Nuchow, William, 1928-1993 (Box 21)
  - Nuffield, William Richard Morris, Viscount, 1877-1963 (Box 21)
  - Nugent, Angela, undated (Box 21)
  - Nye, Gerald P. (Gerald Prentice), 1892-1971, 1939 (Box 21)
- O, 1873-1991; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Oatis, William Nathan, 1914-1997, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Obadele, Imari Abudakari, undated (Box 21)
  - Oberlander, Theodor, 1960 (Box 21)
  - Obraztsov, Sergei, undated (Box 21)
  - O'Brien, M.D., undated (Box 21)
  - O'Brien, William, 1913 (Box 21)
  - O'Casey, Dennis, 1969 (Box 21)
  - O'Casey, Sean, 1880-1964, 1954 (Box 21)
  - O'Connor, Harvey, 1897-1987 (Box 21)
  - O'Connor, James, undated (Box 21)
  - O'Connor, Jessie Lloyd, 1904-, 1977 (Box 21)
  - O'Flanagan, Michael, undated (Box 21)
  - O'Hare, Kate Richards, 1877-1948 I, 1911 (Box 21)
  - O'Hare, Kate Richards, 1877-1948 II, 1920 (Box 21)
  - Ohsol, J.G., 1968 (Box 21)
  - O'Kane, T.J., Rev., 1944 (Box 21)
  - Oler, Edward I, 1937 (Box 21)
  - Oler, Edward II, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Olgin, Moissaye J. (Moissaye Joseph), 1874-1939, 1935 (Box 21)
  - Olivereau, Louise, 1917 (Box 21)
  - Ollenhauer, Erich, undated (Box 21)
  - Olmstead, Frank, 1943 (Box 21)
  - O'Neal, Frederick, 1905-1992, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Oneal, James, 1875 I, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Oneal, James, 1875 II, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Opitz, Edmund A., undated (Box 22)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1904-1967, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Oppenheimer, Martin, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Orans, David, 1964 (Box 22)
  - O'Reilly, Leonora, 1870-1927, 1991 (Box 22)
  - O'Reilly, Mary, undated (Box 22)
  - Ornitz, Samuel, undated (Box 22)
  - O'Rourke, John J., 1964 (Box 22)
  - Orozco, Jose Clemente (catalog of pinturas murales), 1937 (Box 22)
  - Orr, Charles A., undated (Box 22)
  - Orr, Samuel, 1951 (Box 22)
  - Orton, William, 1924 (Box 22)
  - Osgood, William, 1916 (Box 22)
  - Osman, Arthur, undated (Box 22)
  - O'Sullivan, John, undated (Box 22)
  - Otto, Max C., undated (Box 22)
  - Ottley, Roi, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Overstreet, Harry Allen, undated (Box 22)
  - Owen, Robert Dale, 1801-1877, 1873 (Box 22)
  - Owens, Major, 1981 (Box 22)
  - Oxnam, G. Bromley (Garfield Bromley), 1891-1963, undated (Box 22)
- P, 1878-1998; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Pablo, Michel, 1959 (Box 22)
  - Packard, John C., 1934 (Box 22)
  - Padover, Saul Kussiel, 1905-, 1949 (Box 22)
  - Paetel, Karl O., 1952 (Box 22)
  - Paine, Lyman, 1901-1978, undated (Box 22)
  - Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809, 1950 (Box 22)
  - Paish, George, Sir, b. 1867, 1914 (Box 22)
  - Panken, Jacob, b. 1879, 1930 (Box 22)
  - Pannell, Walter, 1944 (Box 22)
  - Papadakis, J., 1967 (Box 22)
  - Papp, Joseph, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Parrish, Richard, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Parsons, Albert Richard, 1848-1887, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich, 1890-1960, 1957 (Box 22)
  - Pat, Jacob, 1890-1966 (Box 22)
  - Patai, Frances S., 1998 (Box 22)
  - Paton, Alan, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Patterson, Ellis E., 1945 (Box 22)
  - Patterson, Joseph Medill, 1879-1946, 1906 (Box 22)
  - Pauker, Ana, 1893-1960, 1947 (Box 22)
  - Paul, Maurice, undated (Box 22)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1901-1994, 1961 (Box 22)
  - Payne, Roger, 1870-1955, undated (Box 22)
  - Pearson, Hesketh, 1887-1964 (Box 22)
  - Peck, James, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Pegler, J. Westbrook (James Westbrook), 1894-1969, 1942 (Box 22)
  - Pelloutier, Fernand, 1909 (Box 22)
  - Peltier, Leonard, undated (Box 22)
  - Pentecost, Hugh O., 1906 (Box 22)
  - Pepper, Claude, undated (Box 22)
  - Peralta, 1946 (Box 22)
  - Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965, 1937 (Box 22)
  - Perkins, William, undated (Box 22)
  - Perlman, Fredy, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Perlman, Selig, 1888-, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Perlo, Victor, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Perlow, Max, 1946 (Box 22)
  - Perry, Ben, undated (Box 22)
  - Perry, Pettis, 1949 (Box 22)
  - Person, Carl, 1914 (Box 22)
  - Pesotta, Rose, 1896-, 1965 (Box 22)
  - Pessl, Yella, undated (Box 22)
  - Petersen, Arnold, 1885-1976, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Peterson, Florence, 1894-, 1940 (Box 22)
  - Philbrick, Herbert A. (Herbert Arthur), 1915-1993, 1941 (Box 22)
  - Phillips, Wendell, 1811-1884, 1878 (Box 22)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973, 1939 (Box 22)
  - Pickus, Robert, undated (Box 22)
  - Pinochet, Amos, 1917 (Box 22)
  - Pinkerton, William A. (William Allan), 1923 (Box 22)
  - Pinski, David, 1872-1959 (Box 22)
  - Pinson, Koppel S. (Koppel Shub), 1904-1961, 1945 (Box 22)
  - Plekhanov, Georgii Valentinovich, 1856-1918, 1895 (Box 22)
  - Plummer, Leslie, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Pointe de Sable, Jean Baptiste, 1745?-1818, undated (Box 22)
  - Pokrovsky, M. N. (Mikhail Nikolaevich), 1868-1932, 1920 (Box 22)
  - Pol Pot, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Poland, William, 1848-1923, 1912 (Box 22)
  - Polikoff, Max, 1961 (Box 22)
  - Polin, Morris L., circa 1935 (Box 22)
  - Pollit, Harry, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Pompei, Giuliana, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Poole, Ernest, 1905 (Box 23)
  - Porter, Paul R. (Paul Robert), 1908-2002, undated (Box 23)
  - Portes Gil, Emilio, 1891-, 1936 (Box 23)
  - Post, Louis Freeland, 1849-1928, 1917 (Box 23)
  - Postgate, Raymond William, 1896-1971, 1934 (Box 23)
  - Potofsky, Jacob S. (Jacob Samuel), 1894-1979, 1926 (Box 23)
  - Potthast, Edward Henry, 1880-1941, 1927 (Box 23)
  - Pouren, Jan Janoff, 1907 (Box 23)
  - Powderly, Terence Vincent, 1849-1924, undated (Box 23)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1908-1972, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Powel, Bernadette, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Powell, John W., undated (Box 23)
  - Prestes, Luís Carlos, 1898-, 1940 (Box 23)
  - Preston, Morris: Smith-Preston Case, 1914-1915 (Box 23)
  - Price, M. Philips (Morgan Philips), 1885-, 1923 (Box 23)
  - Price, William A., undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Priest, Roger, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Pritchard, William A., undated (Box 23)
  - Pritt, D. N. (Denis Nowell), 1887-, undated (Box 23)
  - Proctor, Roscoe, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Proudhon, P.-J. (Pierre-Joseph), 1809-1865, undated (Box 23)
  - Puddington, Arch, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Puente, Isaac, undated (Box 23)
  - Purple, Adam, 1930-, 1998 (Box 23, Box 35, Folder 22)
- Q, 1939-1991; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Quill, John J., undated (Box 23)
  - Quill, Mike, 1939-1966 (Box 23, Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Quill, Shirley, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Quint, Howard H., 1953 (Box 23)
- R, 1910-2005; 3.75 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Racz, Elizabeth, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Radek, Karl, 1885-1939, 1923 (Box 23)
  - Rainey, Homer P. (Homer Price), 1896-, 1944 (Box 23)
  - Ramsay, Caroline R., 1962 (Box 23)
  - Rand, Ayn, undated (Box 23)
  - Rand, Esther, 1972-1977 (Box 23)
  - Randall, Margaret, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Randolf, John, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Asa Philip), 1889- I, 1939 (Box 23)
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Asa Philip), 1889- II, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Rankin, John E. (John Elliott), 1882-1960, 1943 (Box 23)
  - Ransome, Arthur, undated (Box 23)
  - Raskin, A. H. (Abraham Henry), 1911-, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Rattenbury, Owen, undated (Box 23)
  - Rausch, Bernhard, 1918 (Box 23)
  - Rauschenbusch, Walter, 1861-1918, 1916 (Box 23)
  - Raushenbush, Esther, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Raushenbush, Stephen, b. 1896, undated (Box 23)
  - Ray, James Earl, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Ray, Sibnarayan, undated (Box 23)
  - Reagon, Cordell Hull, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Reclus, Élisée, 1830-1905, undated (Box 23)
  - Reeb, James J., 1965 (Box 23)
  - Reece, Florence, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Reed, Eugene T., 1966 (Box 23)
  - Reed, Evelyn, 1975 (Box 23)